orel alon

Full Stack Developer

💌 orela231089@gmail.com 📞 0526707895 👂 israel 🛚 in Linkedin 🔘 Github 🤘 Portfolio 🦻 8200

SUMMARY

As a junior developer I have gained experience in ReactJS, NodeJS, Express, and MongoDB throughmy coding bootcamp education and hands-on project work.

I am comfortable working on both the front-end and back-end of web applications.

In addition to my formal education, I am dedicated to staying up to date with the latest technologies and best practices in the field.

I am an avid **open source** contributor and make a conscious effort to write code every day to keep my skills sharp.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, AppleSeeds Academy

Intensive hands-on 6-months (720 hours) training program, that encourages self-led learning along with group projects that simulate real-world development teams Learning and applying front end skills, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeSript and React, as well as back end skills, including Node-JS and the NoSQL database, like MongoDB, all while using **Git** for source control.

B.A in Economics and Finance, Max Stern Yezreel Valley College

PROJECTS

Foodbook App, *Github* \ *Web* □

- Social food network project allows users to connect with others who share their love for food. By registering, users can upload their favorite food images and share them with their network. Additionally, users can search for their favorite restaurants and see the dishes that are offered there. This project helps bring food lovers together, making it easy to discover new restaurants and dishes to try.
- This application was built using React for the frontend, ExpressJS and NodeJS for the backend, and MongoDB for the database. It also utilizes cloudinary.

Foodbook App

code

Nutrition tracker app, *Github* \ *Web* □

- Advanced calorie intake tracker, built with React, allows users to track their caloric intake based on their personal inputs. With the integration of third-party resources and a **REST API**.

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer, Junex, part time

2022 - present

- Write clean, efficient, and well-documented code to ensure the application is maintainable and scalable.
- Collaborate with a team to ensure the application meets required specifications and performs well.

Economist, Shemen Industries Ltd

2018 - 2021

- Responsible for setting and monitoring annual goals for the sales department, tracking sales and profits on a monthly basis, and analyzing sales data using advanced features.
- Play a crucial role in determining product pricing through analyzing costs and market.

Banker, Discount Bank

2016 - 2018

- Providing financial advice to clients.

- Received numerous awards for excellence, including monthly, uarterly, and annual certificates.

Owner Franchise, Golbary

2012 - 2015

MILITARY SERVICE

Intelligence Unit 8200

Computer Network Manager, responsible for managing and maintaining computer systems for the organization.

orel alon